{
    "id": "c325eec1899e48b090424d33496d1b24",
    "title": "Tenses Exercise",
    "questions": [
        {
            "question": "I waited for him until he …………………",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "comes",
                "came",
                "had come"
            ],
            "correct": 1,
            "id": "51f2961d298f426eaf64914b2c7e3cd2"
        },
        {
            "question": "As long as the rain ………………….., I stayed at home.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "continues",
                "continued",
                "had continued"
            ],
            "correct": 1,
            "id": "2a0b06aa5e7f4a2a976193a68491f6b2"
        },
        {
            "question": "He ran as fast as he ………………….",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "can",
                "could",
                "may"
            ],
            "correct": 1,
            "id": "d22344e6e24f4753803de5c2c63b070f"
        },
        {
            "question": "He was so tired that he …………………. barely stand.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "can",
                "could",
                "would"
            ],
            "correct": 1,
            "id": "54e212d62bdd473c8b1be9385cc5b327"
        },
        {
            "question": "Wherever he …………………, the people gathered to listen.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "preaches",
                "preached",
                "would preach"
            ],
            "correct": 1,
            "id": "2f29e83101f2497b8fc12b8f5dd29def"
        },
        {
            "question": "He ………………. because he was in a hurry.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "run",
                "runs",
                "ran"
            ],
            "correct": 2,
            "id": "5853b3de182343cfbab00a0e1cc5b4c5"
        },
        {
            "question": "Although he began late, he ………………… first.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "was finishing",
                "finished",
                "had finished"
            ],
            "correct": 1,
            "id": "ccb33b20809b4a7eb499697002d7eabc"
        },
        {
            "question": "I asked him what I ……………….. do for him.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "can",
                "could"
            ],
            "correct": 1,
            "id": "9430bc53277d4f309595605be7021362"
        },
        {
            "question": "He said the he …………………. make another attempt.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "will",
                "would"
            ],
            "correct": 1,
            "id": "f799b87b3b97418a9c506940b1d6ee8f"
        },
        {
            "question": "He rested his horse because it ……………….",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "limped",
                "was limping",
                "had limped"
            ],
            "correct": 1,
            "id": "d54f03b155334448a6d0e0947b089fe4"
        }
    ]
}